Yea
Got the lobby going dumb
Oh no
Scoped In
When I hit it make you numb
So low
Drop down
Rolling Out
Since the jump
Lets go
go
go, go
Lets go
go, go, go
go, go, go, go
Yea I got the lobby going dumb
Faster than a Tommy
Boogie out to leave you stunned
Boxin' up to edit, you should really try to run
Sighted in, about to pull the trigger
Make you numb
Everybody wanna be the one too take me down
But I just run it back
I got like 50 bodies going to the lobby
Try to copy but it's not an act
Yea
Got me pumping adrenaline
Been here since the depot
Double pump was the medicine
I remember, architects inventing like Edison
Landing at the towers, ripping bodies
It's menacing
Now I'm stacking all these kills for the thrill
Double jumping like a shadow bomb
Take me to the depot
Fully matted
Keep my ammo long
Adderall
Focused
They don't give me my respect
I've been taking bodies ever since the depot so eject
One time for the drop
Push it to the limit
No I'm never gonna stop
Murder every season
Copping everything in stock
No I never miss a shot
Yea
Got the lobby going dumb
Oh no
Scoped In
When I hit it make you numb
So low
Drop down
Rolling Out
Since the jump
Lets go
go
go, go
Lets go
go, go, go
go, go, go, go
If you hit me, I'll just pop another 50
Got the loot you wanted, come and meet up at Shifty
No more rifting
Caught you on the ground
Why you solo
Trap above your dome
I might hit you with a low blow
Anybody looking' sloppy about to be novelty
I am the best
I got like 50 hobbies but I'd rather put you in the ground
They really should invest
YEAH
Got me pumping adrenaline
Been here since the depot
Double pump was the medicine
I remember architects inventing like Edison
Landing at the towers ripping bodies
It's menacing
Now I'm singing
Squad is wiped
That's an ace
I'm the one that sets the pace
Yeah I'm always in the race
Stacking victories, I'll never be erased
One time for the drop
Push it to the limit
No I'm never gonna stop
Murder every season
Copping everything in stock
No I never miss a shot
Yea
Got the lobby going dumb
Oh no
Scoped In
When I hit it make you numb
So low
Drop down
Rolling Out
Since the jump
Lets go
go
go, go
Lets go
go, go, go
go, go, go, go
Yea
Got the lobby going dumb
Oh no
Scoped In
When I hit it make you numb
So low
Drop down
Rolling Out
Since the jump
Lets go
go
go, go
Lets go
go, go, go
go, go, go, go